My Resume

/online-cv/assets/images/profile.png

Michael Panagiotidis

Blockchain Developer

- p14pana@ionio.gr
- 6981999999
- Thessaloniki, Greece
- \bullet Cpt_MikeEth
- Michail Panagiotidis
- CptMike
- \bullet Cpt_MikeEth

Education

BSc in Computer Science

Ionian University

2014 - 2022

High School Diploma

Anatolia College

2008 - 2014

Languages

• Greek (Native)

- English (Professional)
- French (Entry level)
- Korean (Entry level)

Interests

- Chess
- Cooking

Career Profile

Blockchain developer with 3 years of experience in the Ethereum Blockchain. Friendly and reliable with strong communication and teamwork. Always confident to compete with co-workers, communicate and contribute towards a mutual goal. Accuiring knowledge and experience is the number one priority.

Experiences

Ethereum Engineer Intern

2020 - 2021

Rolla Finance, New York

4 month internship in Rolla Finance. Worked on various projects and contributed to the project to the maximum of my capabilities

- Smart Contracts
- TheGraph
- APIs / Subscriptions

Blockchain Developer Freelancer

2018 - 2020

Freelancing

Worked as a free lancer for small to medium projects on the ethereum blockchain on UpWork.

• Built and deployed ~ 15 smart contracts.

Projects

From 2018 to 2020, I sharpenned my skillset in order to build from scratch a handful of projects.

DEFI Token Exchange smart contract - A project build on Solidity, Javascript, React and Redux. An app on the Rinkeby network, where a user can buy, sell and exchange my Tokens.

Crypto Trading-bot - A project build on Solidity.

Supply Chain Smart contract - A project build on Solidity.

Bugs - A project build on Redux. Showcases store management

Forkify App - A project build on Javascript. Recipe application with custom recipe uploads.

Skills & Proficiency

Javascript & Typescript

Solidity

HTML5 & CSS

React & Redux

 $\mathbf{SQL}\ \&\ \mathbf{PostgreSQL}$

 \mathbf{NodeJs}

Next.js & Ethers.js

webring

Designed with by Xiaoying Riley